https://www.meredith.com/nmg/privacy/marthastewart

YOUR PRIVACY MATTERS
Effective Date: February 12, 2020
Pursuant to a 10-year Licensing
Agreement between Meredith Corporation (“Meredith”) and Martha Stewart Living
Omnimedia, Inc. (“MSO”), Meredith operates and manages MarthaStewart.com, MarthaStewartWeddings.com,
their related mobile applications and the print and electronic editions of the
corresponding magazines (“MSO Properties.”) For the term of this Licensing
Agreement, the Meredith Corporation privacy policy described and hyperlinked to
below will apply to Meredith’s collection, use and disclosure of user
information collected through the MSO Properties. During and after the term of
the Licensing Agreement, MSO, its corporate parent, Sequential Brand Group,
Inc., and their successor companies may also receive any user information
collected through the MSO Properties. To the extent they do, their use may be
subject to their own respective privacy policies.
Hi we are Meredith! Meredith
Corporation and our brands focus on providing you with destinations you can
trust and rely on for every stage of your life to connect you to great content,
products and services and personalize your experience with us.
Our mission is to be clear and
transparent about how and why we collect and use information and to empower you
to control your personal information. You are not our product,
you are our customer.
When Does this Policy
Apply?
This Privacy
Statement applies when you interact with Meredith’s
National Media Group brands (“Brands”) through their websites,
mobile apps, email communications and other platforms (our “Sites”).  To read our EU Privacy Statement click here
What Does it Say?
Read
this policy in full, here.  Here are the highlights:
What Personal Information Do Our Brands Collect about You?
Contact Information (such as name, phone number, postal address or email
address)
Account/Registration Information
(such as user
name and password, reminder questions and answers and
communications preferences, e.g. signing up for a newsletter or
sweepstake, registering for an offer or an experience, or making a
purchase)
Payment Information (such as name, billing address, and credit card
information, e.g. when making a purchase)
Demographic information (such as age, gender race, income, occupation,
marital status, and information about your household/family status,
including your household size and the length of time at your residence)
Online identifiers (such as IP address, internal and third
party identifiers, advertising identifiers and device information
like unique device ID)
Location Data (like your address, city, and zip code, collected in
limited circumstances)
Internet Activity Information (such as browsing history, information on how you interact
with our Sites (e.g. which articles or ads you click on, whether you
click on links in our emails), and your interactions with social media
platform features)
§  Inferences about Your Interests, Preferences and
other Behavioral Data (such as hobbies, and interests (e.g. your
favorite foods, purchases or recipes) and consuming tendencies)
Publicly Available
Information (such as your posts and submissions to blogs, video-sharing
services, and other interactive forums)
MORE
Where/How Do
Our Brands Collect Information About You?
o
From Cookies & Other Technologies (information stored on your browser, which tell us your
browser, device information, IP address, and how you interact with the
Sites).
How Do Our Brands
Use Your Information?
Our Brands use
your information:
To conduct market research and analysis to
understand general trends (how many readers do we have? What content is
popular? Do people prefer video over articles?), our Site visitors, how
ads perform on our Sites (e.g., who clicked on the ad?) and how users
engage on our Sites (e.g. who read that article)
Who Do Our
Brands Share Your Information With?
With
Meredith’s other National Media
Group Brands, which are covered by this Privacy Policy.
With
other companies owned by the Meredith
Corporation, with guidelines in place.
With
our service providers, who help
operate our Sites and provide our services to you.
With
the advertisers who advertise
on our sites or partner with us to send you offers, promotions, or ads
about products and services that may interest you.
With
third party data partners who
help us identify you and who give us additional information about you
that helps us deliver relevant and compelling content and services and
improve the performance of our Sites.
When
required by law
With
a buyer of all or part of our
business.
With
other third parties, when we have
your consent.
MORE
How Can You
Control Our Use of Your Information?
You
can tell us how we can use your information by clicking on the links below:
·       Marketing communications
o
To opt-out
of postal mail from us, please use the opt-out form available here. You can
opt-out from any Meredith email newsletter or other email list by using the
unsubscribe link at the bottom of each message or by visiting the Email preference center.
·       To request deletion or access to your information click here
We
do not knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of 16.
MORE
Rights for
Our California Residents
You
have all the rights listed above. In addition, if you’re a resident of California,
you have the right to:
Request that we not sell your
personal information.
If you would like to exercise this right, click here
Disclose to you whether we
share your information with third parties for their direct marketing
purposes.
o
If you would
like to exercise this right, email us at privacy@meredith.com.
looking for about our data privacy practices? Don’t
worry, just reach out to us at privacy@meredith.com and we will get back to
you!
What
Personal Information Do Our Brands Collect?
When
you visit our Sites, our Brands may collect the following information from or
about you:
§
Online Identifiers: IP address, advertising ID, unique device
ID, and other information about your device, and internal and third party IDs that have been assigned to you.
§
Location Information: Information about your location that you
provide us or that we collect from your device (including city, state, and zip
code) (collected in limited circumstances).
§
Internet Activity Information: Information about your use of our Sites
and other websites you visit, including the web pages, content and
advertisements you view and links you click on, and whether you open, forward
or click the links in emails we send to you, your browsing history, and social
media use including the "shares" and “likes” you make on a social media
platform that is connected to the Sites.
§
Inferences about Your Interests,
Preferences and other Behavioral Data: Hobbies, and interests (like your exercise and
activity levels, your favorite foods, your weight loss objectives and dietary
preferences, which videos you like, your purchases, favorite recipes, or consumption
tendencies).
Some
of our Brands offer you the opportunity to sign up for a newsletter, register
on our Sites, or purchase products from us, when you do that, those Brands may
also collect:
§  Contact
Information:  Your
name, phone number, postal address or email address.
§  Account/Registration
Information: User
name and password, reminder
questions and answers, subscription and account numbers, and communications
preferences (such as which newsletters you would like to receive).
§  Payment
Information: Billing
address, shipping address, credit card or bank account number, expiration date,
and card verification number (when you provide that information to us).
§  Demographic
Information: Age,
gender, race, education level, income information, occupation, marital status,
and information about your household/family status such as the presence of
children/child age ranges, household size, own/rent indicator, and the length
of time at your residence.
Where/How Do We Collect Information About
You?
We collect information about you from a
number of sources:
From
you.  Some of our Brands collect your contact,
registration/account information, and payment information and any other
information when you provide it to us on the Sites.  When you make a purchase on the Sites, we
also retain a record of your purchases and order history.
From
your Device.
What are Cookies & Other
Technologies?
§
Cookies. A “cookie” is a tiny file that’s stored
on your computer. It contains a unique identifier, as well as the address and
other information about the website you are visiting.  Cookies help us know whether you are a
returning visitor to our Sites.  For
example, although you may not log-in when you visit our Sites, we can use
cookies to recognize that you have visited the Site in the past. By using
cookies, we are able to understand what is of interest to our customers and
ensure the content and services we offer are relevant and compelling when you
visit our Sites.  In some cases, we may
use the information we collect from cookies, to deliver relevant and compelling
content to you when you visit the Sites.
§
Web Beacons, Pixel Tags and Other
Tracking Technologies.  Web beacons, pixel techs and other
“tracking technologies” are small strings of code placed on a web page or in an
email or advertisement.  These
technologies allow your browser to recognize and store certain types of
information such as cookies previously set, the time and date that you viewed
the page with the beacon and a description of that page.
Can You Opt Out?
In most cases, yes!  There are some cookies that we need in order
to operate the Sites.  If you deleted
those cookies, the Sites would no longer function (as an example, if we can’t
remember the items you put in a shopping cart, then you won’t be able to place
an order on the Sites).  You can always
decide to opt-out of or delete the third party cookies
(cookies set by Advertisers and Data Partners) on our Sites.  Keep in mind, if you block cookies, you may
not be able to view or access some of the features of our Sites.  Visit our section on your privacy
choices
for more information on how to opt-out.
From
Others.
§  Advertisers.
In some cases, the Advertisers who serve ads
on our Sites will share your email or online identifiers with us so that we can
make sure their advertisements or offers reach you.
§  Data
Partners.  We work with third party data partners
who share information with us about your demographic information, internet
activity information, purchasing information, and your interests, preferences,
and other behavioral data, which help us understand you better and ensure the
content and services we offer are relevant and compelling.
§  Service
Providers. We work with service providers who collect
information on our behalf in order to provide services to us, such as hosting
our websites, processing our credit card transactions, fulfilling your
subscriptions and orders, verifying your identity, and other activities needed
to help us provide our content and services to you.  We only allow our service providers to use
your personal information in connection with the services they provide us.
How Do We Use Your
Information?
We and our other
Meredith Companies and the Service Providers working on our behalf use
information collected about you to:
To
Contact You
§
To
send you emails, including our Brand newsletters, surveys and other
communications.
Fulfill
Your Subscriptions, Orders and Other Requests
§
Fulfill
your orders and requests for products, services, and information (including to
send you email or other newsletters).
§
Some
of our brands offer products and services you can purchase individually or on a
subscription basis. We use the information you provide at check-out to process
your orders on those sites.
Create
and Manage your Account
§  Create and manage your Account, including
providing you with access to your Account.
Marketing
Meredith to You
§
We
may use your information to market the Meredith’s Brands to you, as well as the
products and services of the other companies owned by Meredith.
Personalize
Your Experience on Our Sites, Including the Content and Ads Displayed to You
§
Customize
the content and ads you see when you use our Sites, third party sites, and in
our email communications.
§
Remember
your browser settings and any preferences you set while using the Sites.
§  Recognize you across our Sites so that we
may deliver relevant interest-based content and advertising to you.
Provide
and Improve the Sites
§  Analyze, operate and improve our Sites (including
repairing errors or debugging) or develop new ones.
§
Allow
you to participate in features such as surveys, polls, sweepstakes, and message
boards.
§
Measure
and analyze visitor traffic and usage patterns and improve the quality and
effectiveness of our Sites, features and related communications.
Advertising,
Marketing and other Research for our Advertisers
§  Provide you with special offers,
promotions and information from the Meredith companies, and select third
parties (as permitted by law).
§  To understand trends in how the visitors
to our Sites interact with the ads, content, and features on our Sites (e.g. your
behavior on our Sites may be included in a general report about whether people
prefer video content over written content on our Sites).
§  Help our Advertisers reach you by email.
§
Conduct
market or audience analysis and related reporting (e.g. to give reports on who
our visitors are and whether the ads displayed are effective).
Security
and Fraud Prevention
§
Enforce
our legal rights or comply with the law.
§  Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal
activities, comply with applicable law and enforce our see
the Terms of Service.
We may use your information for any other purposes disclosed
to you at the time we collect your information, provided we have obtained the
required consent.
Who Do We Share Your
Information With?
We
may share your personal information with our other Meredith Companies, Service Providers, Social Media
Platforms, Advertisers, and Third Party Data Partners.
§  Meredith Companies.  The Meredith Brands
covered by this Privacy Statement share your personal information with each
other and will use that information as described in this Privacy
Statement.  Our Brands also share your
personal information with other companies in the Meredith
family, which have their own privacy statements and are not subject to this Privacy
Statement.
§
Service Providers.  We
engage Service Providers to provide services such as credit-card and billing
processing, shipping, marketing, advertising optimization and interest-based
targeting, email and text message distribution, data processing, mobile and
website analytics, user authentication, security and promotions management.  We may share any information we collect about
you with these Service Providers and authorize them to collect information from
you directly to support the services they provide to us.  We do not authorize our Service Providers to
share or use your information with any other third parties.
§
Social Media Platforms.  To
make your experience with our Sites more enjoyable, we may offer features made
available by social media platforms (such as likes or social sharing).  Some social media platforms may collect
information directly from you pursuant to their own separate privacy policies
which may differ from ours. Some social media platforms also act as our data
partners, which means that we may share your personal information with them as
described below under “Data Partners.”
§
Advertisers.  We
are able to provide most of our Sites and other content to you for free with
the help of the Advertisers who promote their products and services on our
Sites.  Brands with ad-supported Sites
share aggregate visitor information with Advertisers, which includes
information about your demographics, Internet activity information, interests
and preferences. In some cases, we share contact information (such as your
name, age, and/or email address) or online identifiers with these Advertisers.  If you sign up for a special email offer from
one of our Advertisers, our Brands will also share your email address and any
other information you provided with your request with the advertisers you
selected.
§
Data Partners. Some of our Brands provide select third party
Data Partners with lists of our user email addresses in a hashed, encrypted or
anonymized form that they use to recognize you.
These Data Partners will provide us with additional information about
you (such as your interests, preferences or demographic information).  Other Data Partners use cookies and other
tracking technologies to enable the delivery of interest-based advertising to
users. We do not authorize our Data Partners to share your email address with
their other clients.
§  Legal Compliance, Business Transfers, and
Other Disclosures.  We disclose information about users of
our Sites when we believe the law requires it. For example, to respond to
compulsory process or law enforcement requests, to enforce our Terms of Service, or
to protect the rights, property or safety of users, the public, Meredith Companies,
Service Providers, Social Media Platforms, Advertisers, Data Partners, or third
parties.  Over time, we may reorganize or
transfer various assets and lines of business. We reserve the right to disclose
or transfer any information we collect to third parties in connection with any
proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease, merger, foreclosure, liquidation,
amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance
or financing of all or any portion of Meredith companies.
How Can You
Control Our Use of Your Information?
What Rights Do You Have?
§  Right to Know: You have the right to ask us to tell you
what personal information we collect use, disclose and sell about you.
§  Right to Request Deletion: You have the right
to ask us to delete the personal information we collect or maintain about you.
§  Right to be Free from Discrimination: You have the right
not to be discriminated against for exercising these rights.
§  Right to Access or Correct Your Information: You have the right
to request access to and to edit certain personal information that you have
provided to us through our Sites.
We are only legally required
to honor these rights in certain jurisdictions, but we
are working towards honoring these rights for all Meredith visitors.  If you are in the U.S. and wish to exercise
your rights:
§  Information and Deletion Requests. To exercise your
right to for information on our data collection practices on this Site or
request deletion of the information on this Site, please use the request form
available here We will need to
verify that you are who you say you are before we delete or share personal
information with you.  After you submit
your request, you will be sent a confirmation email and need to click on the
link provided. If you are a postal subscriber, we may need to request more
information from you in order to verify your request.
What
Other Choices Do You Have?
Marketing
Communications
Postal Mail. To remove your name and postal address
from lists that we sell or rent to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, or to opt-out of receiving marketing offers for other Meredith
magazines and products by mail, please use the opt-out form available here or send your request
to us in a letter addressed to Meredith Corporation, Opt-Out Postal, Attn:
Circulation, 1716 Locust Street, Des Moines, Iowa 50309.
Note that if you choose to opt-out of
Meredith’s promotional mailings, you may still receive renewal notices and
related offers for any magazines to which you subscribe.
Email.
You
can opt-out from any Meredith email newsletter or other email list by using the
unsubscribe link at the bottom of each message or by visiting Email
Preferences
(offered by some of our Brands) on our Sites and updating your preferences. If
you no longer want to receive third party email offers that you requested
through our Sites, simply follow the advertiser's unsubscribe link or opt-out
instructions that should be included in every commercial message you receive.
Opt-Out
of Cookies & Other Technologies.
There are a few ways to opt-out or delete
cookies:
On
your browser (Chrome, Safari, etc.).
The settings of the browser you use give you an option to accept or
reject most cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is
different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to
change your cookie preferences.) Please be aware that certain browsers cannot
block or delete so-called "Flash" cookies, which use a feature of the
Adobe Flash video player to store information on your computer. For information about how to delete Flash cookies, please
visit the Adobe
website  This will opt you out of cookies on the
browser you are using. If you use multiple browsers, you will need to take this
step for all relevant browsers.  Please note that denying all or certain cookies may result in a
less personalized experience of some of the services offered on the website.
Opt-Out
on a Mobile Device. Depending
on your device and operating system, you may be able to reset your mobile
device's advertising identifier to limit this data collection or prevent the
collection of usage data across unaffiliated applications for interest-based
advertising purposes by accessing the privacy settings on your mobile device.
Each operating system, iOS for Apple devices, Android for Android devices and
Windows for Microsoft devices, provides its own instructions. Visit the privacy
settings for your mobile device or contact your platform operator for more
information.
Opt-Out
of Nielsen’s Tracking Technologies.
Some of our Advertisers and Brands may use Nielsen’s measurement
services, which contribute to market research, like Nielsen’s TV and Online
Campaign Ratings service.  Nielsen’s
pixel may be in some of the ads on our Sites and will record whether or not you
viewed the ad.  Nielsen uses the data it
collects to create ratings reports for advertisers and publishers.  For more information about Nielsen's
information collection practices and any related opt-out choices, please see
We
follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral
advertising.
§  To opt-out of our use of your website
viewing data to serve interest-based advertising on third party websites and
email newsletters, visit the DAA’s Consumer Choice Page
§  You can also click on the Ad Choices
located in the footer of our websites and navigate to the consumer opt-out
form.
§  Most of the third party
advertising and data companies we work with, including DoubleClick and Google
also subscribe to the DAA Principles and/or are members of the Network
Advertising Initiative ("NAI"). To learn more about the information
collection practices of NAI members and your related opt-out choices, please
visit the NAI's
website
§
You
must opt-out separately from each computer or device and browser that you use
to access our Sites and if you clear your cookies, you will need to repeat the
opt-out process.
**Note that many of
our websites allow you to adjust your cookie preferences. You can find these
controls in the footer of our websites.
Mobile App Advertising and Tracking
Some of our brands may collect
information about your mobile device, including unique advertising identifiers
and the names and IDs of apps you have installed, as well as information about
how you use our mobile applications and other unaffiliated applications. We and
our partners use this information to enable interest-based advertising you
receive through our Sites and within third party apps and other marketing
channels.
For information about
the mobile data collection practices of the service providers we use to support
interest-based advertising in our AllRecipes mobile applications and your
additional opt-out choices, click here and here
Do
Not Track
We do not currently respond to browser do-not-track signals.
Instead, we adhere to the standards set out in this Privacy Statement and offer
the opt-out choices described above.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly
allow anyone under the age of 16 to provide us with any personal information
online. Children should always get permission from their parents before sharing
any personal information about themselves over the Internet. If you're under 16,
please do not register for the Sites or provide us with any personal
information.
Additional
Privacy Information
§  Contests and Other Co-Sponsored Promotions.  From
time to time, we may offer contests, sweepstakes or other promotions.
Participation in these promotions may require registration on our Sites.  We may share your registration information with
co-sponsors or other third parties involved in the promotion that we identify
in the rules or entry materials. We don't control these third parties' privacy
practices, and our Privacy Statement does not apply to their collection and use
of your information. We may also share some of your entry information with
third parties or the public in connection with the administration of the
promotion, such as winner selection and prize fulfillment, and as permitted by
the promotion's official rules, such as on a winners' list.
§  Security, Retention and Storage of
Information.  We use commercially reasonable procedures
to protect the information that we collect. However, we cannot guarantee the
security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply
won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Please
see our  Terms of Service for more information related to posting
materials on our Sites including our use of such materials.
§  Location of Your Data.  Meredith is a U.S. company and your personal
information will be transferred to, processed, stored and accessed by us, the Meredith
Companies and Service Providers in the United States and in other jurisdictions
where we or they operate, which may not provide you with the same level of
privacy protection as you are entitled to in your jurisdiction.
EU-U.S. Privacy Shield.  Meredith
adheres to the principles of the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework (“Privacy
Shield Principles”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding
the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the
European Union (“EU”) to the United States, and it is in the process of
certifying its compliance with the U.S. Department of Commerce.  If there is any conflict between the terms in
this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield
Principles will govern.  To learn more
about the Privacy Shield program, please visit the Privacy Shield website.
Meredith is responsible for the processing of personal information
it receives under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, or subsequently
transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Meredith complies
with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers from the EU and
EEA, including onward transfer liability provisions.
The U.S. Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over
Meredith’s compliance with its obligations under the EU-U.S. Privacy
Shield.  In certain situations, Meredith
may be required to disclose personal information in response to a lawful
request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law
enforcement requirements.
In
compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Meredith commits to resolve
complaints about our collection or use of your personal information.  EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding
our Privacy Shield policy should first contact us at privacy@meredith.com. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us,
or if we have not resolved your complaint, you may submit your complaint at no cost to you to JAMS, our independent recourse mechanism, at https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield.
In the event there are residual complaints that have not been resolved by JAMS, or any other means, you may seek a non-monetary remedy through binding arbitration to be provided you in accordance with the Privacy Shield Principles.
§
Changes to Our Privacy
Policy.  Digital technology is rapidly evolving.
If we decide to change our Privacy Statement in the future, we'll post the
changes here and indicate at the top of the policy the last date on which it
was updated. Unless otherwise noted, all changes will be effective when posted.
Rights for Our California Residents
This
section contains information on the personal information we collect about residents
of California (our “California Consumers”), including the sources of that
information, how that informed is used, who it is shared with, and the rights
that California Consumers have under California law. Our collection of your
information, our data sharing practices, and your privacy rights are discussed
below.
I.      Our Collection of
Your Information
What
Information Do We Collect About You?
Where
Do We Collect this Information From?
Why
Do We Collect this Information?
Who
Do We Share this Information With?
Contact Information (Name, Email, Postal Address, Zip Code, Telephone Number)
§ From you when you register on our sites, subscribe to one of our
publications, or otherwise submit this information to us.
§ From our
Advertisers who place ads on Services.
§ From our
Data Partners (these are companies who give us
information about you to help us and our Advertisers understand who you are
and what you may be interested in).
§  To contact
you (to deliver our newsletters,
surveys, and other communications to you).
§  To fulfill
your subscriptions, orders and other requests.
§  To market
our Services to you.
§  To create
and manage your account when you
register on our Services and provide you with your membership benefits.
§  To combine
with other information we receive from our Data
Partners to help us learn more about you, your interests and preferences so that we can customize your experience
on our Services (including the content and advertisements displayed to you).
§  To deliver
targeted advertisements to you on
social media platforms or other third party
websites.
§  To help our Advertisers
contact you.
§  To help us measure
the effectiveness of the ads on our Services, including to understand
whether you click on the ads on our Services and whether you buy the
products/services advertised.
§  To prevent fraud,
including verifying your identity
§ Service
Providers (companies who use your personal
information solely to provide services to us, including advertising, website
support, analytics, payment processing, subscription/order fulfillment and
customer service).
§ Data
Partners (these are companies who we share
personal information with to help us identify potential customers, and to
understand who you are and what you may be interested in).
§ Our
Advertisers (the brands that advertise on our
Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
§ Social Media
Platforms.
§ Other Meredith
Brands and Companies.
Account/Registration Information
(Name, username, and password)
§ From You when you create an account or register on our Services.
§To create
and manage your account when you
register on our Services and provide you with your membership benefits.
§ Service
Providers (companies who use your personal
information solely to provide services to us, including advertising, website
support, analytics, subscription/order fulfillment and customer service).
Demographic Information (age, race, gender)
§ From You when you share that information with us on surveys,
registration or other forms on our Services.
§ Data
Partners (these are companies who give us
information about you to help us and our Advertisers understand who you are
and what you may be interested in).
§ To create
consumer segments (groups of cookies and other IDs
based on information we collect about, for example “Women age 35-44 who have
purchased mascara.”, which we share with advertisers looking to sell mascara
or products we think people who like mascara may also be interested in).
§ To serve
targeted ads to you (to  help us, our advertisers, and our
advertising networks and platforms to identity the best ads to display to you
on our Services, based on the Interests, Preferences and Other Behavioral
Data associated with your online identifiers).
§
To help us identify you and understand your interests and preferences so that we can customize your experience
on our Services (including the content and advertisements displayed to you).
§ Service
Providers (companies who use your personal
information solely to provide services to us, including advertising, website
support, analytics, subscription/order fulfillment and customer service).
§ Our
Advertisers (the brands that advertise on our
Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
§ Other Meredith
Brands and Companies.
Online Identifiers (IP addresses, device IDs, and other internal and third party identifiers we use to recognize you online)
§ From Pixels,
Cookies, and Other Tracking Technologies, which collect information about
you when you visit our Services online.
§ Data
Partners (these are companies who give us
information about you to help us and our Advertisers understand who you are
and what you may be interested in).
§ To create
consumer segments (groups of cookies and other IDs
based on information we collect about, for example “Women age 35-44 who have
purchased mascara.”, which we share with advertisers looking to sell mascara
or products we think people who like mascara may also be interested in).
§ To serve
targeted ads to you (to  help us, our advertisers, and our
advertising networks and platforms to identity the best ads to display to you
on our Services, based on the Interests, Preferences and Other Behavioral
Data associated with your online identifiers).
§
To help us measure the effectiveness of the ads on our Services,
including to understand whether you click on the ads on our Services and
whether you buy the products/services advertised.
§ Service
Providers (companies who use your personal
information solely to provide services to us, including advertising, website
support, analytics).
§ Data
Partners (these are companies who we share
personal information with to help us identify potential customers, and to understand
who you are and what you may be interested in).
§ Our
Advertisers (the brands that advertise on our
Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
§ Other Meredith
Brands and Companies.
Online activity information (browsing history, search history, information about your
interactions with our Services)
§ From Pixels,
Cookies, and Other Tracking Technologies, which collect information about
you when you visit our Services online.
§
Data Partners
(these are companies who give us information about you to help us and our
Advertisers understand who you are and what you may be interested in).
§ To create
consumer segments (groups of cookies and other IDs
based on information we collect about, for example “Women age 35-44 who have
purchased mascara.”, which we share with advertisers looking to sell mascara
or products we think people who like mascara may also be interested in).
§ To serve
targeted ads to you (to help us, our advertisers, and
our advertising networks and platforms to identity the best ads to display to
you on our Services, based on the Interests, Preferences and Other Behavioral
Data and Online Activity associated with your online identifiers).
§
To help us measure the effectiveness of the ads on our Services,
including to understand whether you click on the ads on our Services and
whether you buy the products/services advertised.
§ Service
Providers (companies who use your personal
information solely to provide services to us, including advertising, website
support, analytics).
§ Data
Partners (these are companies who we share
personal information with to help us identify potential customers, and to
understand who you are and what you may be interested in).
§ Our
Advertisers (the brands that advertise on our
Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
Other
Meredith Brands and Companies.
Payment Information
§ From you when your place an order on our Services.
§  To fulfill
your subscriptions and orders, and any refund
requests.
§ Service
Providers (companies who use your personal
information solely to process your payments on our behalf).
Interests, Preferences and other
Behavioral Data (including purchase behaviors)
§ Data
Partners (these are companies who give us
information about you to help us and our Advertisers understand who you are
and what you may be interested in).
§ From Pixels,
Cookies, and Other Tracking Technologies, which collect information about
you when you visit our Services online.
§
To create consumer segments (groups of cookies and other IDs based on information we
collect about, for example “Women age 35-44 who have purchased mascara.”,
which we share with advertisers looking to sell mascara or products we think
people who like mascara may also be interested in).
§ Service
Providers (companies who use your personal
information solely to provide services to us, including advertising, website
support, analytics).
§ Data Partners (these are companies who we share personal information
with to help us identify potential customers, and to understand who you are
and what you may be interested in).
§ Our
Advertisers (the brands that advertise on our
Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
Other Meredith Brands and
Companies.
II.
Our Data Sharing Practices
We
share the personal information below with our Service Providers. Our Service
Providers help us send our newsletters to you, fulfill your orders, provide
advertising and marketing services, and analytics, and other activities that
support our business Service Providers only use the personal information we
share with them to provide these services to us.
Below
are the categories of personal information we disclose to our Service
Providers:
Interests,
Preferences and other Behavioral Data
Data We Sell to
Third Parties
In
some limited circumstances, some of our Brands share your personal information
with third parties who we allow to use that information for their own
commercial purposes.
Below
are the categories of personal information that some of our Brands sell to
third parties:
§  Contact Information
§  Online Identifiers
§  Online Activity Information
§  Interests, Preferences and other Behavioral Data
III.
Your Privacy Rights
What
Rights Do You Have?
§  Shine the Light Rights – You have the right
to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, a list of the
third parties to whom we have disclosed certain types of personal information
(if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year. At our
option, we may respond to such requests by providing instructions about how our
users can exercise their options to prevent our disclosure of personal
information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.
§  Right to Opt-Out of a Sale of Personal Information – You have the right to ask us not to
sell your information to third parties.
IV.      How
Do You Submit These Requests to Us?
In
addition to the rights detailed in the “How Can You Control Our Use of Your Information?” section above, California residents can:
§  Contact us to exercise your Shine the Light Rights at privacy@meredith.com.
§
Opt-Out of Sales.
To opt-out of the sale of your personal information on this website click here.
Corporation. Privacy Statement or its implementation please contact us via
email by clicking here or by writing to:
